Alexander, Gabriel Arbitration Files 5133
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Deere and Company. (Box 6)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 6952-20, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-119, 68-120, 68-121, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Deere and Company. (Box 7)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-9, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-10, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-11, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-12, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-13, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-19, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-15, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 68-18, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-17, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec. 69-1083, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec., 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Dec., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Case 70-1, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Case 70-2, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - John Deere Horicon Workers and Local 873, I.A.M. -and- Local 433 International Molders and Foundry. Workers of America, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-3, 1965-1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 1910-4, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-5, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-6, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 1970-7 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-8, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-9, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-10, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-11, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-12, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-13, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-14, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-15, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Deere and Company -and- U.A.W. Case 70-16, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Detroit Gasket and Mfg. Co. - Evans Products Co.. (Box 8)
  - Detroit Gasket and Mfg. Co. Marine City Div. -and- Local 1114 UAW-CIO, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Det. Gravure Corp. -and- Local 12, Det. Photo Engravers, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Detroit Harvester - UAW Local 155, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - AAA - Detroit Millmen's Fund, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Detroit Newspapers - I.B.E.W., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Doehler-Jarvis, Div. of National Lead Co. -and- Local 257, UAW and National Doehler-Jarvis Council, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Greyhound Lines -and- Amalgamated Transit Union Driver Schroeder Discharge Gr. E-37-65, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Greyhound Lines -and- Div. 1210 AASERMCE of A. (Girard case), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Michigan Distr. Inc. -and- Teamsters Local 458, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Elliot Company and United Steel Workers of America, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Evans Products Co. -and- Local USW., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Evans Products - Steelworkers CIO, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Evans Products Co. -and- United Steelworkers Dist. 29, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Fairbanks, Morse and Co. - General Motors (Delco Products Div.). (Box 9)
  - Fairbanks, Morse. Local 922, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ford Motor Company -and- Pattern Makers Association, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ford Motor Company -and- Pattern Makers' Association of Der. And Vicinity The Pattern Makers' League of N.A., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Garland Mfg. Co., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Garwood, Wayne, Mich. -and- Local 250, UAW, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gar Woods Industries, Inc. United Metal Craft Division -and- Local 769, UAW, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gemmer Mfg. Co. Div. of Ross Gear and Tool Co. Inc. -and- Local 80 UAW-AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - General Controls Company Iron Mountain, Michigan -and- I.A.M., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - GM-Chev. Mfg. Co. (Flint) -and- Local 659, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - GM-Chev. Div. Mfg. (Flint) -and- UAW, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Delco Products Feb. 1948 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Delco Appliance Division; Rochester, New York, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Delco - Local 755 March 1948 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Delco appliance Division, General Motors Corp. -and- IUE-CIO Local 509, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Delco Prod. Div. GM (Dayton) -and- Local 755 IUE-CIO, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- General Motors (Frigidaire Div.). (Box 10)
  - Frigidaire D 52-61, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Frigidaire C29-D-19 and D-26, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - General Motors Flint Mfg. Div. -and- UAW, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - General Motors - Frigidaire Division May 16-17-18, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - GM-Frigidaire -and- IUE Dayton, Ohio, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - General Motors - Frigidaire + IUE, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - General Motors - Frigidaire UEW-CIO, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Frigidaire F-126-F13, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Frigidaire, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- General Motors (Frigidaire Div.) - M.A. Banna Co.. (Box 11)
  - General Motors - Frigidaire Div. I.U.E., 1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - GM - Inland Manufacturing Co., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - GM- Inland Mfg. Co. (Dayton) -and- Local 87, U.R.C.L.W.A. AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - GM-United Motors U.E.R.M.W.A. Chicago, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - GM - Umpire Case, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - General Motors United Electrical etc. Correspondence and Misc. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Richard Electric December 1947 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Richard Electric Division 1948 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - GM-Buick Flint Retail Stores -and- Local 741, UAW, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Grand Rapids Metalcraft -and- Local 19, UAW, AFL-CIO (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Grand Rapids Metalcraft -and- Local 19, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Grand Rapids Metalcraft -and- Local 19, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Guardian Glass Co. -and- Local 174, UAW, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - M.A. Hanna Company -and- United Steelworkers of America Houghton, Michigan, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Heppenstall Co. - Jervis Corporation. (Box 12)
  - Heppenstall Co. -and- Local 2651, USW., 1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ind and Mich. Elec. Co. -and- I.B.E.W., 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Rubber Goods Co. St. Joseph, Mich. -and- Local 210 United Rubber, Cork, etc., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Inland Steel Container Co. -and- USE, District 28, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - International Salt Co. Inc. -and- International Chem. Workers, Union, Local 48, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Rubber Goods Co. St. Joseph, Mich. -and- Local 210, United Rubber, Cork, etc., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Inland Steel Container Co. Gr. USW District 28, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - International Salt Co. Inc. -and- International Chemical Workers Union, Local 48, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Ironrite, Inc. IUE Local 990, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Ironrite Corp -and- Local 990 IUE-AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ironrite Corporation -and- Local 990 IUE-AFL-CIO Mt. Clemens, Michigan, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Ironrite, Inc. -and- Local 990 IUE-AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Grand Rapids Metalcraft UAW-CIO, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Jersey Creamery-, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Jervis Corporation -and- Local 356, UAW, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. (Pittsburgh Works, 11/7/60); Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. (Aliquippa (4/4/60). (Box 13)
  - New Docket (17-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - New Docket (18-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - New Docket (19-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - New Docket (20-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - New Docket (21-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - New Docket (22-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - New Docket (23-C-60), 1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - New Docket (24-C-60), 1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - New Docket (25-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - New Docket (26-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - New Docket (27-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - New Docket (28-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - New Docket (29-C-60), 1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - New Docket (30-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - New Docket (31-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - New Docket (32-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - New Docket (33-C-60), 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - New Docket (1-C-60), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - New Docket (35-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - New Docket (36-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - New Docket (37-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - New Docket (38-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - New Docket (2-C-60), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. (Pittsburgh Works, 4/25/1960); Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. (Aliquippa Works, 6/13/60). (Box 14)
  - New Docket (3-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New Docket (4-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - New Docket (5-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New Docket (6-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - New Docket (7-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - New Docket (8-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - New Docket (9-C-60), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - New Docket (1-C-60), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - New Docket (11-C-60), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - New Docket (13-C-60), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - New Docket (14-C-60), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New Docket (15-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - New Docket (16-C-60), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - New Docket (39-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. (Pittsburgh Works, 12/4/61, 3/10/61). (Box 15)
  - New Docket (40-C-60), 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New Docket (41-C-60), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - New Docket (42-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - New Docket (43-C-60), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - New Docket (44-C-60), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - New Docket (45-C-60), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - New Docket (47-C-60), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - New Docket (48-C-60), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - New Docket (49-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New Docket (50-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - New Docket (51-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - New Docket (52-C-60), 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - New Docket (53-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - New Docket (54-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - New Docket (55-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - New Docket (56-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - New Docket (57-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - New Docket (58-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - New Docket (59-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - New Docket (60-C-60), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - New Docket (61-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - New Docket (62-C-60), 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - New Docket (63-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - New Docket (64-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - New Docket (65-C-60), 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - New Docket (66-C-60), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. (Aliquippa Works, 10/3/60 - 7/27/61). (Box 16)
  - New Docket (67-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - New Docket (68-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - New Docket (69-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - New Docket (70-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - New Docket (71-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - New Docket (72-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - New Docket (73-C-60), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - New Docket (74-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - New Docket (75-C-60), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - New Docket (76-C-60), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - New Docket (77-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - New Docket (78-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - New Docket (79-C-60), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - New Docket (80-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - New Docket (81-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - New Docket (82-C-60), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - New Docket (83-C-60), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - New Docket (85-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - New Docket (86-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - New Docket (87-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - New Docket (88-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - New Docket (89-C-60), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Cancelled cases with old Docker or no Docket Numbers, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - New Docket (90-C-60), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - New Docket (91-C-60), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - New Docket (92-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. (Aliquippa Works, 10/3/60 - 7/27/61). (Box 17)
  - New Docket (93-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - New Docket (94-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - New Docket (95-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - New Docket (96-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - New Docket (97-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - New Docket (98-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - New Docket (99-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - New Docket (100-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - New Docket (101-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - New Docket (102-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - New Docket (103-C-60), 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - New Docket (104-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - New Docket (105-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - New Docket (106-C-60), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - New Docket (107-C-60), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - New Docket (108-C-60), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - New Docket (109-C-60), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - New Docket (110-C-60), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - New Docket (111-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - New Docket (112-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - New Docket (113-C-60), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - New Docket (114-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - New Docket (115-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - New Docket (116-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - New Docket (117-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - New Docket (119-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - New Docket (120-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - New Docket (121-C-60), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - New Docket (122-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - New Docket (123-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - New Docket (124-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. (Pittsburgh Works, 11/1/61); Jones and Laughlin (Aliquippa Works, 12/7/60). (Box 18)
  - New Docket (125-C-60), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - New Docket (126-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - New Docket (127-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - New Docket (128-C-60), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - New Docket (129-C-60), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - New Docket (130-C-60), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - New Docket (131-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - New Docket (132-C-60), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - New Docket (133-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - New Docket (136-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - New Docket (137-C-60), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - New Docket (138-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - New Docket (140-C-60), 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - New Docket (143-C-60), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - New Docket (144-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - New Docket (145-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - New Docket (146-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - New Docket (147-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - New Docket (148-C-60), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. (Aliquippa Works, 1961, 1962). (Box 19)
  - New Docket (152-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - New Docket (150-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - New Docket (153-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - New Docket (154-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - New Docket (158-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - New Docket (159-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - New Docket (162-C-60), 1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - New Docket (163-C-60), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - New Docket (173-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - New Docket (184-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - New Docket (185-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - New Docket (186-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - New Docket (190-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - New Docket (196-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - New Docket (199-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - New Docket (200-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - New Docket (211-C-60), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - New Docket (212-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - New Docket (213-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - New Docket (217-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - New Docket (218-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - New Docket (235-C-60), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- KVP Sutherland Paper Co. - McLouth Steel Co.. (Box 20)
  - KVP Sutherland Paper Co. Kalazamoo, Michigan -and- Local 1010 United Papermakers, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Karzamin Products Corp. -and- Local 13765, Dist 50, UMV, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Kellogg Company -and- Local 3, Amer. Fed. Of Grain Millers, AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Kelsey-Hayes Company Gr. NL-1 -and- Local 114, UPGWA, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Kelsey-Hayes Co. -and- Local 78, UAW, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Keystone Mfg. Co. -and- I.A.M., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - King Seeley Corporation, Ann Arbor, Michigan -and- Local 630, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Gr. Detroit Chapter of Painting Decorating Contractors of America -and- Dist. Council No. 22 of Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - AAA- Kuhlman Elec. Co. Bay City, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lafayette Steel Co. -and- UAW, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lansing Drop Forge Co. -and- United Automobile etc. Gr. 781, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lear Mfg. Co., 1954 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Lear, Incorporated, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Lear, Inc. -and- Local 330, UAW, AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Lear, Inc. -and- Local 330, UAW-CIO, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Lear Inc. - UAW CIO Local 330, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Lear Incorporated (Work Assignment Policy), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Lear, Inc. -and- Local 330, UAW-AFL-CIO Gr. 1307, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Lear, Inc., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Light Metal Corporation -and- U.A.W., 1959 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Light Metal Corp. -and- UAW, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Light Metal Corporation -and- U.A.W., 1959 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Al. Long - Teamsters, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - The Lufkin Rule Co. -and- Local 452, UAW-CIO-AFL, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Lufkin Rule UAW-CIO Saginaw Hicks, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Lufkin Rule - UAW-CIO, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - The Lufkin Rule Co. Saginaw -and- Local 452 UAW-CIO, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Lyon, Inc. -and- Local 174, UAW, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Lyon Inc. - Local 174 - UAW, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - McInerney Spring - Local 687 - UAW, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - McLouth Steel Corp. -and- United Steel Workers of America, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - McLouth Steel Co. -and- Un. Steelworkers Am. AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - McLouth Steel Co. -and- United Steel Workers of America, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - McLouth Steel Corp. -and- United Steelworkers Local No., 1959 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Marathon Linen Supply Co. - Ohio Edison Co.. (Box 21)
  - Marathon Linen Supply Co., 1959 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Markette Inc. -and- T.W.U.A. -CIO, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Massey-Ferguson, Inc. -and- Local 174, UAW, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Massey-Ferguson, Inc. -and- Local 174, UAW Gr. 636 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Massey-Ferguson, Inc. -and- Local 174, UAW Gr. 659, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Metalcraft UAW, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Michigan Bakeries, Inc. -and- Local 87 United Dairy and Bakery Workers, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Michigan Seamless Tube Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Michigan Seamless Tube Co. -and- United Steelworkers Local, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Mich. Standard Alloys, Inc. -and- Local 2140, IAM, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Michigan Steel Tube Prod. Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Monsanto Chemical Co. Miamisburg, Ohio -and- Local 11-4200 OCAW International Union (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Monsanto Chemical Co. Trenton Plant -and- Local 11-196, Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Moynihan Bronze Co. -and- Shopmen's Local 754, International Iron Workers, AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Geo. L. Nankervis Co. -and- Local 15001, Dist. 50 UMWA, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - National Brewing Co. -, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - National Distillers - Oil Workers, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - New York Air Brake Co. -and- International Association of Machinists, Kalamazoo, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - North Range Mining Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - North Range Mining Co. Penokee Mine - Ironwood -and- United Mine Workers, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Northwestern Steel and Wire Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Northwestern Steel and Wire Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Northwestern Steel and Wire Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - The Ohio Boxboard Co. -and- Local 15-, Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Ohio Edison Company -and- UMWA, Local 118 Gr. 65-26, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Ohio Power Co. - Pennsalt Chemicals Corp.. (Box 22)
  - Penn Salt Chemical -and- Teamsters Local 236, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Pennsalt Chem. Corp. -and- Local 12100 UMWA, Dist. 50 Gr. 863, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Pennsalt Chemicals Corp. -and- United Mine Workers of America Dist. 50 Local 12100, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Penn Salt Grievance. 623, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Penn Salt-, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Penn. Salt Mfg. Co. -and- UMWA, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Penn salt Chem. Corp. -and- Local 12100, United Mine Workers, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Salt Mfg. Co. -and- Local 12100, United Mine Workers of America, Dist 50, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Salt Mfg. Co. -and- Local 12100, United Mine Workers of America, Dist 50, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Penn Salt Mfg. Co. -and- United Mine Workers of America Dist. 50, Local 12100 Grievance. 830, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Pennsalt Chemicals Corp. -and- Local 12100, United Mine Workers of America, Dist. 50 Gr. 931, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Penn. Salt company (Grievance 645) United Mine Workers, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Penn Salt 693-702, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Penn Salt - UMW Grievance. 630, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Parke Davis Co. - I.A.M. Mar. 12, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 15)